{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "ja",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "1st",
      "answer": "一日"
    },
    {
      "question": "2nd",
      "answer": "ニ日"
    },
    {
      "question": "3rd",
      "answer": "三日"
    },
    {
      "question": "4th",
      "answer": "四日"
    },
    {
      "question": "5th",
      "answer": "五日"
    },
    {
      "question": "6th",
      "answer": "六日"
    },
    {
      "question": "7th",
      "answer": "ヒ日"
    },
    {
      "question": "8th",
      "answer": "八日"
    },
    {
      "question": "9th",
      "answer": "九日"
    },
    {
      "question": "10th",
      "answer": "十日"
    },
    {
      "question": "14th",
      "answer": "十四日"
    },
    {
      "question": "20th",
      "answer": "ニ十日"
    },
    {
      "question": "24th",
      "answer": "ニ十四日"
    },
    {
      "question": "31st",
      "answer": "三十一日"
    },
    {
      "question": "30th",
      "answer": "三十日"
    }
  ]
}
